{
    "id": "7f39ce8af059413da720690248d80a65",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Not until that day …………………………. able to recover her confidence.",
            "description": "When not until comes at the beginning, we use an inverted word order.",
            "answers": [
                "she was",
                "was she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63d8bd7f51ea457289822efa607682cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I stay …………………….. Saturday?",
            "description": "We use until to talk about a situation that will continue up to a certain moment.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "by",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b4389a5ff7349ef8ffaab6b2ceb3384"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can repair your stereo …………………………….. Friday.",
            "description": "We use by to say that an action will happen at a future moment.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until",
                "within"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a05b922dd77e43ffa9374fc59a1683a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The nearest supermarket is about half a mile …………………………… the highway.",
            "description": "Sometimes both up and down can be used to mean along or further on.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "07283e0d24504ef192b5bf0a10288c80"
        },
        {
            "question": "You surprised ……………………………",
            "description": "There is no preposition between surprise and its verb.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "with me",
                "at me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d2eb4e96e874df7967cf39538554adc"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………………….. the railway station in half an hour.",
            "description": "There is no preposition after reach.",
            "answers": [
                "reached",
                "reached at",
                "reached to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35af4d74de05478da4e32148aff821c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to ……………………….. Mary some flowers.",
            "description": "Buy can be followed by a direct object and an indirect object. There is no preposition when the indirect object goes before the direct object.",
            "answers": [
                "buy",
                "buy for",
                "buy to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d28829248da4fde975e9fe61d474cbb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s …………………………. your plans.",
            "description": "Some verbs need a preposition before their object.",
            "answers": [
                "talk",
                "talk about",
                "talk of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8b30eaea35f4fde82542c1a79e8a3a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you staring ………………………. like that?",
            "description": "Some verbs need a preposition before their object.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "at me",
                "to me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c439334d4c3147fd98defeacdd81f5bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I am going to jump over the stream.",
            "description": "The preposition is dropped when there is no object.",
            "answers": [
                "Look",
                "Look at",
                "Look on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0be72f63aaa24c36afc94e780d3cedbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrived ……………………………… the station in the morning.",
            "description": "A preposition is usually used before an expression of place. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "794c1ef90b8042bca3d34c0ae69ab0d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We seem …………………………….. a problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to have",
                "having",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7cac472519ce4fefbb5d2ace6364f16b"
        }
    ]
}